Enjoy the glory of your victory, chosen children of the Phi Brain.
（真方ジン）選ばれし　ファイ・ブレインの
子供たちに　勝利の祝福を…。→
残ったのは
やはり　お前たちだったか。
You two prevailed, just as I expected.
友情や愛…　人間のくだらぬ感情を
超越したようだな。
You appear to have overcome those foolish human emotions like friendship and love.
（大門カイト）くそっ　オルペウス！
（レイツェル）どういう事？
Damn you, Orpheus!
What do you mean?
大門カイトは見捨てたのだ。→
Daimon Kaito let them die.
ギャモンと　フリーセルをな。
Gammon and Freecell.
（ジン）
これで　お前たちは資格を得た。→
You've earned the right
神のパズルに挑む資格を…。→
to challenge the Puzzle of God.
どちらかが　ファイ・ブレインとなり
我が　新たな器となる…。
One of you will become the Phi Brain and my new vessel.
明日　神のパズルを始める。
You will face the Puzzle of God tomorrow.
また会おう
ファイ・ブレインの子供たちよ。
See you soon, children of the Phi Brain.
神のパズルは　俺一人で解く。
レイツェル　お前は来るな。
I'll solve the Puzzle of God by myself.
Don't come, Raetsel.
え？
オルペウスは　俺が必ず封じ込める！
I'm gonna seal Orpheus away.
これ以上の犠牲は　必要ない。
There's no need for any more sacrifices.
（イワシミズ君）
補助バッテリー接続。　エネルギー充填完了。
Additional batteries connected.
Additional batteries all charged.
（キュービック・Ｇ）
これで　準備は整ったね。
カイトたちとの合流を急ごう。
We're all ready now. We should hurry up and meet with Kaito and the others.
The problem now is how to get into Amgine, I guess.
（軸川ソウジ）問題は　どうやって
アムギーネに入るか…　だね。
（ピノクル）抜かりはないさ。
アムギーネの防空警戒網を無効化し→
No worries.
I'll disable Amgine's air defense systems,
その間に強行着陸する。→
so that we can make a quick landing during that time.
It's hacking time.
じゃあ…　ハッキング開始だ！
（無線・男性）「飛行中のＰＯＧ機
飛行中のＰＯＧ機。→
To the approaching POG vessel. To the approaching POG vessel.
This is the Amgine International Airport Air Traffic Control.
こちらは　アムギーネ国際空港管制室。→
The president has sent you a message.
大統領からのメッセージを
お伝えします。→
『アムギーネ共和国へ　ようこそ。
君たちを歓迎する。→
"Welcome to the Republic of Amgine.
"I am happy to receive you in our country.
誘導に従い　速やかに
入国手続きをしたまえ』。→
"Please follow the landing guidance and the passport control procedures."
繰り返します…」。
I repeat.
（井藤ノノハ）
カイト　一体　何があったの？
カイトってば！
Kaito, just what happened?
Kaito!
（姫川エレナ）
ねえ…　ギャモンたちは　どうしたの!?
Tell us. What happened to Gammon and Freecell?
Sorry, but could you leave me alone?
悪ぃ…　一人にしてくれ。
カイト！
Kaito!
（キュービック）あっ　いた！
キューちゃん！　みんな…。
There they are!
Cubie! Guys!
ノノハ！　カイトは？
Nonoha, where's Kaito?
Kaito! It's me, Kaito!
カイト！　僕だよ　カイト！→
出来たんだ！　対オルペウス用の
秘密兵器が。
（イワシミズ君）エッヘン　エッヘン。
I've finished the anti-Orpheus weapon!
オルペウスが転送しようとする瞬間に
特殊電磁パルスで遮断する！
The moment Orpheus tries to change bodies, I'll stop him with a special EMP!
うまくいけば
みんな助かるかもしれないんだ！
If it all works out, then it may save everyone!
（キュービック）カイト？
何かあったようだな。
Kaito...
Looks like something happened.
パズルから戻ってきてないの…
ギャモンたち。
Gammon and Freecell didn't return from the puzzle.
The ship was burning... Don't tell me Gammon—
船が燃えてた…。
まさか…　ギャモン…。
（解道バロン）
大丈夫。　２人とも無事ですよ。
Don't worry. They are both all right.
Principal? When did you arrive in Amgine?
学園長！　いつ　アムギーネに？
あらかじめ…　です。
Just now.
カイト君たちが
大統領の船に招待されたとの→
We got word they were invited to the president's yacht,
情報が入りましたので→
万が一に備え　救出班を
待機させておいたのです。
so we had a rescue team standing by just in case.
Blowing up the entire ship was a bit unexpected.
まさか　船ごと爆破するとは…。
Gammon and Freecell suffered some wounds during their escape though.
ギャモン君と　フリーセル君は
脱出の際　少し　けがをしたため→
They are under the POG's protection, and are currently hospitalized abroad.
ＰＯＧで保護しました。→
今は　国外の病院で
手当てを受けていますが→
They are both alive and well.
２人とも元気ですよ。
ほんとに!?
Really?
（イワシミズ君）よかった　よかった。
Glad to hear. Glad to hear.
They got injured, huh? I was wondering why he stopped texting me.
（メランコリィ）けがしたですって!?
突然　メールが来なくなったと
思ったら　そういう事でしたのね。
Melancholy? Even you're here?
メランコリィ！　君まで来たの？
ハァ…　まったく
心配ばかりかけて。→
I can't believe how much he dared make me worry.
まあ　わざわざ
プリティーメランコリィ　サブマリン号で→
I'm relieved to know I rushed here in the Pretty Melancholy submarine for nothing though.
来るほどの事では
ありませんでしたわね。
You've been texting Freecell? Since when?
君とフリーセルが　メール!?
いつの間に？
あら！　あなたでも
ご存じない事があったのね。
Oh? There are things you don't know about?
僕以外の友達ができたのは
うれしいけど→
I'm glad he made friends other than me,
黙っているなんて　ひどいな
フリーセル。
but he shouldn't have kept it secret.
今度　文句を言ってやらないと。
（エレナ　ノノハ）フフフッ。
I'll complain when I see him next time.
学園長。　ルーク管理官の事
何か　ご存じじゃありませんか？
Principal, do you happen to know anything about Chief Rook?
連絡がつかなくなっているんです。
We lost contact with him.
Oh, you didn't get word?
おや？　そちらには
連絡が行っていませんか。
「独自に調べたい事があるので
別行動をとるが→
He wanted to investigate something by himself so he's operating on his own.
We got a message from him telling us not to worry.
心配しないでほしい」。　管理官から
そう連絡がありましたよ。
Oh, I see.
な～んだ
そうだったんだ。
よかった。
That's good.
（イワシミズ君）めでたし　めでたし。→
Glad to hear. Glad to hear.
めでたし　めでたし。
「ギャモン君も　フリーセル君も無事」
ですか…。
So Gammon and Freecell are all right?
本当の事　教えて頂けませんか？
学園長。
Could you tell me the truth now, Principal?
やはり　君には隠せませんか…。
So I couldn't fool your eyes after all?
We're searching for them with everything we've got, but there's been no luck so far.
総力を挙げて
２人を捜索していますが→
見つかったという連絡は
いまだ…。
ルーク管理官は？
What about Chief Rook?
（バロン）数日前　アムギーネ国内で
カイト君を呼び出したあとから→
He's been missing since he called Kaito a few days ago in Amgine.
消息不明です。→
We found a giant duel puzzle underground though.
調査の結果　地下に　巨大な
対戦型パズルを見つけました。→
ここで２人は　パズルで対決。→
It's highly likely they fought there and Chief Rook lost.
ルーク管理官は敗北し　恐らく…。
なぜ　みんなには　うそを？
Why would you lie to the others?
真実を知れば　これ以上
パズルに関わらせまいとして→
Because if they knew the truth, they would try to stop Kaito from challenging any further puzzles.
皆で　カイト君を
止めようとするでしょうから。
Kaito must challenge the Puzzle of God if we want to eliminate Orpheus.
オルペウスを止めるためには→
カイト君に　神のパズルに
挑んでもらわねばならない。
彼の心を乱す雑音は
少ない方がいいでしょう。
The less distractions the better.
You want to push all the responsibility onto Kaito?
そうやって　カイト君に　全ての責任を
負わせようというのですか!?
そもそも　神のパズルを巡る
全ての出来事は→
Isn't this whole mess about the Puzzle of God yours and Jin's fault?
あなたとジンさんが…！
I am aware how deplorable acting like this is as an adult and as a person.
大人として…　いや　人として→
最低の行為だと理解しています。
But is there any other way?
ですが　他に方法がありますか？
We can't even become the Phi Brain.
ファイ・ブレインになる
資格すらない我々に…。
学園長。　僕も
ギャモン君たちの捜索に加わります。
Principal, let me join the search for Gammon and Freecell.
ファイ・ブレインになれなくても
やれる限りの事はしたいんです。
Even if I can't become the Phi Brain, I want to do everything in my power to help.
（オーブンのベル音）
（エレナ）ノノハ　焼けたわよ。
Nonoha, they're ready!
These are the stamina cookies for Kaito.
こっちは
カイトに差し入れする　スタミナクッキー。
お見舞い用の　エネルギーマカロンっと…。
These are the energy macarons for the injured.
どうして私が　こんな事を…。
Why do I have to do this?
Move your hands not your mouth!
しゃべってないで　手を動かす！
It's Freecell's get well present!
フリーセル君への
大事な　お見舞いなんだから。
もうすぐ　神のパズルが始まる。
The Puzzle of God will begin soon.
私たち女子チームは
私たちのできる事をやりましょ！
We, the girls team, should do all we can too.
でも…　神のパズルって
とんでもなく難しい上に→
But the Puzzle of God is not only extremely difficult,
we don't even know what's gonna happen to the winner and the loser.
勝った方も　負けた方も
どうなるか分からないんでしょ？
Will Kaito be all right?
カイト　大丈夫なの？
当たり前じゃない！
Of course!
Gammon and Freecell are fine too. I'm sure it's gonna work out this time as well.
ギャモン君も　フリーセル君も
無事だったんだし→
今度だって　きっと大丈夫。
I hope you're right.
だといいのですけど。
えっ？
Hmm?
He still hasn't come out of his room, has he?
だって　ずっと部屋に
籠もったままなのでしょう？→
大門カイトは。
う…　うん。
Gammon... Freecell... Rook...
ギャモン…　フリーセル…　ルーク…。
懐かしい…　この感じ。
This atmosphere brings back memories
心の声
（レイツェル）ジンと旅してる頃
よく来たな。→
of the time I was traveling with Jin.
待っててね　ジン。
あした　全てが終わる。→
Just a little longer, Jin.
It'll all be over tomorrow. I'm gonna save you for sure.
あなたは　私が必ず助ける。
I'll solve the Puzzle of God by myself.
回想
神のパズルは　俺一人で解く。
レイツェル…　お前は来るな。
Don't come, Raetsel.
心の声
（レイツェル）カイト…。
Kaito...
Crap!
≪あ～　くっそ～。
Once more!
もう一回だ！
お兄ちゃん…。
But...
絶対　あれを取るんだ。
パパの誕生日プレゼントに。
I'm gonna get that!
It's for Dad's birthday!
Here I go...
よ～し…。
そんなんじゃ
駄目だよ　お兄ちゃん。
That won't work! You should aim higher!
狙うのは
もっと上の方が…。
Oh, shut up! What do you know?
うるさい！　お前は黙ってろ！
（レイツェル）こ～ら　ケンカは駄目でしょ。
Hey, don't fight.
What are you even doing? Give it back!
（兄）何すんだよ！　返せよ！
（レイツェル）ふ～ん　あれが欲しいんだ。
だったら→
So you want that?
Then you ought to listen to your sister.
妹のアドバイスを聞いた方がいいわよ。
えっ？
（妹）えっと…　えっとね…→
Um... Um...
一緒に取ろう！　お兄ちゃん。
Let's get it together!
Right... You're right. That'd make Dad happier too.
（兄）そっか…　そうだよな。
その方が　パパも喜ぶよな。
えっと…
上の方を狙うんだっけ？
うん！
Aim higher, right?
こんな感じか？
もうちょっと　上！
Like this?
A bit higher!
よ～し！
Here I go!
やった～！
やった　やった！
Yay!
Hurray!
心の声
（レイツェル）「一緒に」か…。
Together, huh?
（店員）
おめでとう。　はい　景品のサングラス。
Congratulations. Here's your prize, the sunglasses.
Yay!
（妹）わ～い！　やった　やった～！
レイツェル…。
Raetsel?
カイト　気に入ってくれるよね。
I hope Kaito will like it.
I'm gonna shove it down his throat if he doesn't.
文句　言ったら
ぶちのめして　さしあげますわ。
（ノック）
≪カイト　入るよ？　スリー　ツー　ワン。
Kaito, I'm coming in!
Three! Two! Go!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ジャジャーン！　みんなで作った
元気の出る…　あれっ？
We made these cheer-up co—
Huh?
He's not here?
おりませんの？
So rude. We made them for his sake too.
何よ！　せっかく
作ってあげたのに。
（レイツェル）う～ん　迷っちゃうわね。
どれもこれも　おいしそうで。
I can't make up my mind. Everything looks so delicious.
あっ！　これ　いいかも。
This will do!
おじさん　２本　ちょうだい。
あいよ。
Two of these, please!
Gotcha.
毎度あり。
Thanks!
何のつもりだ？　レイツェル。
What are you doing, Raetsel?
見てられないわね　その顔。
I couldn't bear to see that look on your face.
今の君じゃ　私の相手は
務まりそうにないわ。
You wouldn't stand a chance against me the way you are now.
I have no intent of dueling you.
勝負はしない。　神のパズルから
手を引けと言ったはずだ。
I told you to withdraw from the Puzzle of God.
オルペウスを目覚めさせたのは俺だ。
俺が一人で　オルペウスを倒す。
I was the one who awakened Orpheus.
I'll beat Orpheus by myself.
神々への挑戦…。
Challenging the gods... So many things have been sacrificed for that stupid dream of his.
やつの　くだらねえ目的のために
いろんなもんが　なくなった！
これ以上　俺は　誰も犠牲に…。
I don't want anyone else to—
うっ!?
うるさいわねえ　まったく。
Oh, shut up already.
な～にが
「人間の感情を超越した」よ。
And he said we've overcome human emotions.
Orpheus's got no idea.
オルペウスも分かってないわね。→
Daimon Kaito, the way you are now, I'm not gonna lose to you.
大門カイト。
今の君には絶対負けない。→
ううん…　今の君じゃあ
どんなパズルも解けない。
Or rather, you wouldn't even be able solve any puzzles right now.
だって　今の君の目
死んじゃってるもの。
Your eyes are so lifeless.
大事なものを失う覚悟なんて→
You weren't ready at all to lose something dear to you.
何にも
できていなかったって事よね。
But that's fine.
でも…　それでいいのよ。
君は人間なんだもの。→
It just makes you human.
私には想像もできない
つらさだわ。→
I can't even imagine how tough it must be.
Having to abandon the friends you love...
大好きな仲間を
見捨てなくちゃいけないなんて。
ねえ　カイト…。　君が　そこまでして
神のパズルに挑むのは　何のため？
Kaito,
why are you going so far to challenge the Puzzle of God?
私は　ジンを救うため。
I'm doing it to save Jin.
Are you doing it to stop Orpheus?
君は
オルペウスを倒すため？→
Or to protect those dear to you?
それとも
大切な人たちを守るため？
お…　俺は…。
I—
ネギ!?　これ　ネギじゃねえか。
Huh? Onions? These are onions?
フッ　大丈夫。　アムギーネのネギは
私でも食べられるくらい→
It's okay. Even I can eat the Amginean onions. They're so sweet and soft.
甘くて　柔らかくて　おいしいから。
あ…　本当だ。
You're right.
よかったわね　味が分かって。
Glad you liked it.
え？
ノノハが言ってたでしょ。
Remember what Nonoha said?
「おいしいものを食べたら
大抵の事は解決する」って。
Delicious food can solve most problems.
うん。　確かに　うめえ…　このネギ。
These onions really are good.
でしょ？
Right?
「何のために」か…。
Why am I doing this, huh?
ありがとな　レイツェル。
見失ってたぜ　大切な事。
Thanks, Raetsel.
I lost sight of what's really important.
ギャモンや　フリーセルに見られたら
また　ぶっ飛ばされてるところだ。
If Gammon and Freecell saw me like that, I'd be in for a few more punches.
（レイツェル）パズルは鎖　パズルは鏡。→
Puzzles are chains. Puzzles are mirrors.
私たちは　ジンという鎖で結ばれた
鏡合わせの２人。
We are bound by a chain called Jin. We are on opposite sides of the same mirror.
仲間じゃないけど→
Even if we're not best friends, there's something we need to work together to achieve.
私たちが力を合わせなきゃ
できない事がある。
一緒にやりましょ　カイト。
Let's do this together, Kaito. In order to protect what's important to us.
大切なものを守るために…
ふたりで！
The two of us.
Yeah.
あっ　キューちゃん　どうだった!?
Cubie, any luck?
駄目だ。　どこにも　いないよ。
（イワシミズ君）いない　いない。
Not at all! We couldn't find him anywhere!
Nowhere. Nowhere.
どうして　何も話してくれないのよ
カイトのバカ！
Why won't he tell us anything? That stupid Kaito.
Sorry!
悪ぃ。
ん？
Kaito!
（ノノハ　キュービック）カイト！
ありがとな　ノノハ。
Thanks, Nonoha.
Man, Nonoha sweets are as good as always!
やっぱ　うめえぜ！　ノノハスイーツ！
えっ？
キュービック。　秘密兵器
作ってくれたんだって？　サンキュー。
Cubik, did you say you made some secret weapon against him?
Thank you.
（イワシミズ君）どういたしまして。
どういたしまして。
You're welcome. You're welcome.
学園長　先輩
みんなも　いろいろ　すまねえ。
Principal, Jikukawa, sorry for all the trouble.
Kaito...
カイト君。
あした　俺たちは　神のパズルに挑む。
We're gonna challenge the Puzzle of God tomorrow.
みんなの未来は　絶対　俺が守る。
I'm gonna protect everyone's future.
そして　必ず帰ってくる。
And I'll be back.
ジンと　レイツェルと…　３人で。
Together with Jin and Raetsel.
カイト。
Kaito...
That's settled!
≪（エレナ）これで解決ね！
じゃあ　これ食べましょ。
Let's eat up!
What's this?
≪これって何だ？
≪（メランコリィ）
私たちの作った　スイーツですわ。
Sweets we made.
You? Baked?
≪（ピノクル）君たちが料理？
≪（メランコリィ）失礼ですわね。
So rude!
You cheered Kaito up, right, Raerae?
（アナ・グラム）
レイレイが元気にしてくれたんだね
カイトを。
Ana?
（レイツェル）アナ！
アナが思うに　お礼しなくちゃ。→
I think... we should thank you!
行こう！　レイレイ。
（レイツェル）えっ？　あっ　ちょっと…。
Come on, Raerae!
Hey, wai—
（アナ）みんな～！
（レイツェル）わ～!?
Guys!
Raetsel?!
（ソウジ　キュービック　ノノハ　エレナ）レイツェル！
（レイツェル）わ…　私　帰るから。
I was just about to leave...
あら　泊まっていきなさい。→
Please do stay.
一緒に
神のパズルに向かうんでしょ？
You'll be challenging the Puzzle of God together, won't you?
でも…。
レイツェルさん。
But...
Raetsel, I really wanted to chat a bit with you once.
あなたとは　一度　お話をしたいと
思っていましたの。
いろいろ　趣味が合いそうですし。
I think our tastes are quite alike.
レイツェルがいると　なんだか
あの女子会を思い出すわね。
This reminds me of that girls' day out.
That what?
えっ？　何それ。
Right?
Uh...
That's not fair! I wanna be part of the girls' fun too!
ずるい！
私もやりたい　女子会！
あら　いいですわね。
Sounds like a plan!
盛大に　おもてなし
してやってくれ！
Make sure she feels at home!
よっ。　喜んで！
あぁ!?　わっ…。
Will do!
みんな　女子部屋に移動よ！
お～！
To the girls' room!
Hey! What?
ちょ…　ちょっと　何!?
Let the girls' night part two "in Amgine" begin now!
（エレナ）それでは　これより
第２回　女子会　イン　アムギーネを→
始めま～す！
（ノノハ　エレナ　メランコリィ　アナ）イェーイ！
Yay! Girls' night! Clappity-clap!
わ～！　女子会　女子会！
パチパチパチパチ。
Uh, I...
あの…　私…。
いいから飲みなさい　イチゴジュース。
Just drink up.
It's strawberry juice.
大事なのは　ギャップよ。
クールに見えて　実は純情とか。
What matters is maintaining the gap
by playing it cool while actually being innocent and pure.
Like Raerae?
レイレイみたいに？
あ～　分かる！　確かに。
Oh, you're right! Totally!
You heard them.
（メランコリィ）ですってよ。
どうなんですの？　レイツェル。
How is it, Raetsel?
I... don't really know.
そ…　そんな事ないと思うけど。
似合ってる　似合ってる。
It looks great on you!
プリチー！
（エレナ　メランコリィ　ノノハ）かわいい！
So cute!
Raerae!
Now you've crossed the line!
やったわね…　えい！
う～ん…。
違う。　そこ引っ張って。
No! No! Pull that there!
Wrong! Why would you turn it that way?
あ～　違う。
何で　そこ下げるのかしら？
あ～　駄目　駄目。
何やってんの。
What are you even doing?
Looking there won't help you.
そこ　のぞいたって
しかたないですわ。
んぐ～…　無理！
I can't do it!
（メランコリィ　エレナ）あ～！
あ…。
（エレナ）何してんのよ～。
（メランコリィ）信じられませんわ。
What are you doing?
Unbelievable.
あ～　おっかしい。　やっぱり
あなたたちって面白いわ。→
So funny! You girls are so funny.
いいわね　仲が良くって…。
It's nice how you all get along.
（アナ）レイレイも　その中に入ってる。
Then join in.
えっ？
みんなも　レイレイと仲良し。
Let's all get along, together with Raerae.
Not everyone can put on an Armlet for someone they love.
大好きな人のために
その腕輪をつけるなんて→
なかなか
できる事ではなくってよ。
I'd love to talk more with you.
もっと　もっと　お話したいですわ
あなたと。
Me too! So make sure you come back.
私も！
だから　ちゃんと帰ってきてね。
また　女子会の続きをしましょ。
We should continue these girls' parties.
みんな…。
Girls...
Gammon...
ギャモン…。
フリーセルの…　アホー。
Freecell, you jerk!
You finally showed yourself, villain!
出たな　くせ者！
とりゃ～！　とぉ～…。
I only have Jin.
心の声
（レイツェル）私には　ジンしかいない。
ジンだけいれば　いい…。→
I only need Jin.
そう思ってた。
That's what I thought.
回想
（アナ）みんなも　レイレイと仲良し。
Let's all get along, together with Raerae.
心の声
（レイツェル）うれしかった…。→
I was happy.
うれしくて
おいしくて→
Everything was so delicious, happy, and fun.
楽しかった。→
ジンの思い出と同じくらい…。
It was almost like a memory of Jin.
Thank you, everyone.
心の声
（レイツェル）ありがとう　みんな。
レイツェル…。
Raetsel...
I think... we'll see her again!
アナが思うに…　また会えるよ。
約束したから。
（鳴き声）
She promised.
（イワシミズ君）全システム　オールグリーン。
スタンバイ完了。
All systems ready to go.
Standing by.
よし！　行こう　カイト。
Okay. Let's go, Kaito.
Not with that robot.
（エニグマ）そのロボットだね。→
It might get in the way of my reunion with Lovushka.
私とラヴーシュカの再会を
邪魔しようとしているのは。
（バロン）ザガートカ！
Zagadka!
Confiscate it.
運び出せ。
（キュービック）えっ…　ちょっと！
Hey!
うっ！　ド…　ドクトル。
わ～!?　な…　何するんだ！
What are you doing?!
Doctor! Doctor!
（イワシミズ君）ドクトール！
（キュービック）イワシミズ君！
Iwashimizu!
（イワシミズ君）アイル　ビー　バック！
I'll be back!
では　行こうか　大門カイト。→
Shall we go then, Daimon Kaito? To the Puzzle of God.
神のパズルへ…。
行ってくるぜ　みんな！
I'm off, guys.
必ず帰ってきてね　カイト！
Come back in one piece, got it? Kaito!
Sure!
This is the Puzzle of God?
これが　神のパズル…。
覚悟は　よいか？
ファイ・ブレインの子供たち。
Are you ready, children of the Phi Brain?
Yeah.
Yes.
What is this?
これは…　一体…。
What kind of puzzle is this, Orpheus?
どういうパズルなんだ!?　オルペウス！
ルールは　自分で見つけるのだ。
Find out the rules yourselves.
（レイツェル）な…!?
くそっ！
Dammit.
Find the goal of your lives yourselves.
（ジン）人生の目的を
自分で見つけるようにな。
始めよう　神のパズルタイムを…。
It's the puzzle time of god.
心の声
（レイツェル）私の色が　赤。
次に進める場所は　あそこね。
I'm the color red. I can move on in that direction.
心の声
移動して　自分の陣地を
増やしていく…。
So we've gotta move and increase our territories.
陣取りパズルって事か。
It's a territory puzzle...
フッ…　その過去を選んだか。
Oh, so you picked that time?
This is my old home...
心の声
（レイツェル）ここは…　昔の私の家…。
何のまねだ…　オルペウス！
What's this about, Orpheus?
This is a puzzle beyond time and space.
（ジン）これは
時間と空間を超越したパズル。→
It's a maze through time.
時の迷路…。
自分の過去を変え
そして　つかみ取るのだ。
Change your own past to reach the future
ファイ・ブレインとなる未来を…。
where you become the Phi Brain!
Preview
I can clearly see the difference between the one who becomes the Phi Brain